- I cannot believe you got us
in to see All Time Low.
- What. like we could miss
the comeback tour?
Seeing them was our first date.
- Yeah. but how did you even
afford the tickets?
The show was sold out.
- Five years married.
You deserve the best
for our anniversary.
- Meaning I don't want to know.
- [laughs]
I love my wife!
Oh.
Whoa.
Sorry about that. guys.
- Why don't you watch
where you're walking?
- Calm down.
It was an accident.
- Calm down?
You want to go right now?
- OK. OK.
My--my husband
had a few too many.
He didn't mean anything by it.
He's sorry.
No harm. no foul. right?
You guys have a nice night.
It's Fleet Week.
What. are you trying
to start a fight
with the whole freaking Navy?
- I could take him.
'cause your love
makes me strong.
- [laughs]
OK. I love you too.
Come on. let's get you home
before you try
and fight the Army too.
[gunfire]
[tense music]
♪ ♪
- I'll be honest. it's a lot.
But I've taken the time.
and I've really
let myself feel all of it.
And I know that grief
is a process.
It's gonna come and go.
But I have been
taking care of myself.
And I just had my last session
with my EAP counselor.
and he agrees.
I'm ready to be back.
- I got his recommendations.
but I have to sign off
that you are OK
to return to the field.
Maggie. losing your sister.
that was an incredible trauma.
And you said
the exact same things
after losing your husband.
verbatim.
- I wish I could say
I haven't been here before.
but I have.
- I'm--I'm just--
I'm worried.
Are you saying
what we need to hear?
- No.
The man who killed
my sister is dead.
I got justice for Erin.
I mean. as much I could.
It wasn't the same thing
with Jason.
It took me years
to get closure for him.
Isobel. I'm good.
[knocking]
- Are you ready
to get back into it?
Jubal just flagged a double
homicide in Flatbush.
- I'm ready.
- OK.
[soft dramatic music]
♪ ♪
OA. keep an eye on her.
- I always do.
- Hey. I wanted to say
thanks for checking in
on me back in Indiana.
You really--
- I know.
- Yeah.
- If I lost my sister.
you would've done the same
for me.
- I know.
- FBI?
- Yeah.
- Detective Hill. NYPD.
- Uh.
Special Agent Maggie Bell.
This is Special Agent Zidan.
We got a call.
- Yeah. the wife there.
she's a federal employee.
Office of Inspector General.
- Guess we're up to bat.
- Sorry to pass the buck.
- What can you tell us?
- Mel. her husband.
Charlie Hakkenson.
Executed after leaving
a show at Kings Theatre
late last night.
Working theory
is gang initiation.
kids killing random civilians.
Wrong place. wrong time.
It happens.
- Any witnesses?
- Some sailors on shore leave
from Fleet Week.
They called 911.
I was just about
to interview them.
- We can handle that.
Thanks. Detective.
- Sure thing.
Good luck.
- Thanks.
- I exchanged some words
with the husband.
but we were walking away when
I heard the tires squeal.
- So they weren't on foot?
- A dark van pulled up
next to them.
Driver sprayed them
with a pistol.
It was over in a second.
- Over in a second?
There's two dozen shell casings
on the ground.
It couldn't have
been that fast.
- It was automatic.
Had an extended clip.
Never seen anything like it.
We ran over to try to help.
maybe do CPR.
but they were clearly dead.
That's when I called 911.
- Did you happen
to get a visual
of the assailant. or a plate?
- Sorry. ma'am. no.
It was dark.
- OK.
Thanks for your help.
- They're all .40 caliber.
Pretty common.
- Yeah. I'll get them
to Ballistics.
Also. we should check out
the security cams.
Maybe we can ID
the assailant that way.
I mean. gang initiation?
I don't know.
- And she's back.
What are you thinking?
- Well. I mean.
popping off this many rounds
and making sure they were dead?
That doesn't sound random.
That sounds targeted.
♪ ♪
- All right. people.
I need a coffee and a sitrep.
Talk to me.
- So Mel and Charlie Hakkenson.
age 32 and 33.
shot dead late last night
after a show
in Flatbush.
- All right.
We finding any reason
why somebody
would have wanted them dead?
- Not really.
Social media
indicates they were
happily married five years.
We're following up
with family and friends.
but so far. it doesn't sound
like the Hakkensons
had any enemies.
Nothing's jumping out.
- Well. nothing yet. but
we're just warming up. right?
Marnie.
you didn't have to do that.
You're my new favorite.
[chuckles]
Oh. wait.
We--we have a video. don't we?
- Yes. Maggie and OA
found a camera
that caught the shooting.
- We get a look at the shooter?
- Uh. no. but we ID'd the van.
NYPD reported it stolen
two days ago.
although no footage
of the theft.
- OK. But we found casings
at the scene. right?
We get anything from that?
- Yes. Ballistics ran it.
Ejector marks on the underside
of the casings
confirm that weapon
is a Glock pistol.
Best guess. given it was
chambered in .40 cal.
Glock 22.
- Wait. wait.
But the witness said
he saw an automatic. right?
- Yeah. it was probably
modded with illegal parts.
Using an autosear.
you can turn any pistol
into a fully automatic
spray-and-pray handgun.
- OK.
Any way to trace the mods
through the shells
or something?
- Unfortunately. no.
Streets are swarming
with modified handguns.
ERT is dusting casings
for prints.
but not holding my breath.
- Right. so a whole bunch
of nothing so far.
But clearly. somebody wanted
this married couple dead.
so let's open up
their story a bit.
Where do they work?
Where do they play?
Any red flags?
- Charlie worked at
the Port of New York
as a longshoreman.
unloading freight.
Not so much as a parking ticket
on his record.
- Mel was an analyst with the
Office of Inspector General.
Investigated complaints
of fraud and waste
inside the federal government.
- Right. she--she basically
pissed people off for a living.
I can relate.
There could easily be
a motive there. right?
So let's bring her boss in.
see what Mel was working on.
- OIG employees.
they get threats all the time.
Now we got these citizen
journalists digging in
on everything we do.
We get paid peanuts
to keep people honest.
and then--
now this?
I'm sorry.
- It's OK.
Uh. what did Mel do. exactly?
- She was an analyst.
Just crunching numbers.
making sure they lined up.
- And these are all
of her active audits?
- Yeah. Mel oversaw
just a handful of NGOs.
federal contractors.
- And if she stumbled
upon something
during one of these audits?
- She would have flagged it.
and then she would have
reported it to me.
- There something
you want to tell us. Abe?
[tense music]
- Look. Mel was
a great employee.
Never any issue.
I knew I could count on her.
you know?
Three days ago.
I get this alert.
Mel had logged into one of
our digital forensic tools
after hours.
completely off-book.
not tied to any
approved investigation.
She was digging into some guy.
his personal life.
way out of bounds.
I was gonna confront her
about it...
today.
I don't know what
she was looking for.
but nothing good was
gonna come out of it.
♪ ♪
- We're gonna need a name.
- All right. folks. eyes up.
One of our vics was running
an off-book investigation
into this man.
Donny Slimkowski.
So run him through
your systems. yeah?
All right. what do we know?
- OK.
Donny. 34. born and raised
in New Brunswick.
He's got a spotty work history.
but he was busted
in 2014 for armed carjacking.
Sentenced to 15 years
in New Jersey State Prison.
paroled out two weeks ago.
Last known address
is his mother's house.
- OK. this--
this sounds promising.
Can we connect
the thread between
Mel Hakkenson and Donny?
Who was he to her?
Why was she looking into him?
- Yeah. took a deeper dive
into Mel's social media.
Looks like she.
Charlie. and Donny.
they all knew each other
from high school.
They were friends.
- Uh. more than friends.
Mel and Donny used to date.
Even signed a lease
together in 2013.
- Right. so they were
getting serious.
- A New York lease?
That's commitment to me.
- Yeah. but while Donny
was in prison. it ends.
And plot twist--
Mel marries Charlie.
sends Donny a note to explain.
It's in his file.
because afterwards.
he sends her a series
of threatening letters
until he loses mail privileges.
- OK.
Let's--let's track him down.
yeah?
This is easy math. right?
Donny goes to prison.
Mel breaks up with him
and then marries
his old pal. Charlie.
And nine years later.
Donny gets out.
He's a scorned. jilted lover
looking for payback.
And Mel. concerned that
Donny's out. looks him up.
- Boss.
- Yeah. where's Donny now?
- A plate reader just picked up
a vehicle registered to him
crossing the Brooklyn Bridge.
- Have a team pick him up.
♪ ♪
- Donny Slimkowski. FBI!
Damn it. he's booking it!
[suspenseful music]
Hey!
- Hey!
♪ ♪
- Get off me!
- Let's go.
On the ground now!
- [grunting]
- Donny Slimkowski.
you're under arrest.
[tense music]
♪ ♪
Mel and Charlie are dead?
- Spraying 20 rounds
into people
can have that effect on them.
- We're not telling you
anything
that you don't already know.
- Wait. wait. wait. wait. wait.
I didn't have anything
to do with this.
When was this?
- Donny. stop. all right?
We know that you were
in love with Mel.
You went to prison.
she broke your heart
and married your best friend.
- I did not--
I would never hurt
Mel or Charlie.
When was this?
- When?
- Yeah.
when'd they get killed?
- 11:30 last night.
- In the city?
- In Flatbush.
- Yeah. see. I was in--
I was in Jersey all night.
I--I have to be.
It's part of my parole.
I can't leave the state.
- Donny. my partner fed you
New York State pavement
not more than an hour ago.
- That's why I ran.
I didn't want to get violated.
I stayed at my cousin's
last night in Jersey.
There's. like. four people
who can vouch for me.
- So what were you doing
in the city today?
- [sighs]
Charlie had something going on.
Easy money. he said.
He said he'd cut me in.
He called. like. a week ago.
knew I got out.
Life-changing money. he said.
- All right. I'll bite.
So what can you tell us
about this life-changing
money scheme?
- The ports.
Uh. his boss
had it all figured out--
they were smuggling things
in through the ports.
That's what he said.
♪ ♪
They're really gone.
- Yeah.
♪ ♪
- All right.
So this is Charlie's boss?
- Yeah.
Ron Strumberger. 58.
He's been a longshoreman
for 20 years.
foreman for six.
He's divorced.
Kids are with the ex-wife.
Seems like a solid citizen
on paper.
- Any criminal record?
- Uh. misdemeanor drunk
in public from 15 years ago.
Otherwise. no.
- All right.
so what is he moving
to generate all this cash?
Drugs. guns. what?
- Whatever it is.
maybe he didn't want
Charlie's ex-con buddy
cut in on it.
- Oh. yeah.
Loose lips sink ships.
So shady foreman Ron
flies off the handle.
silences his guy
for getting sloppy.
That plays.
Where's Ron now?
- His phone is pinging at home.
- Mid-workday.
Let's go have a chat.
- [sighs]
Maggie.
- I see it.
[ominous music]
♪ ♪
Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm
OA.
- That looks like an eyeball.
- Yeah.
[exhales]
♪ ♪
Whoa.
- Ron Strumberger.
- What's left of him.
[tense music]
- All right.
so Ron Strumberger.
a person of interest
in our double homicide. just up
and found himself murdered.
which either makes it
a triple homicide
or. I don't know.
maybe this is
an eye for an eye
kind of thing.
- No way he could
have been involved
in the hit on the Hakkensons.
Preliminary ME report
on Ron came in.
He was tortured and killed
roughly 18 hours before.
- Right. OK.
So he smuggled something
through the port
and runs afoul of the people
he's working with.
and so they--they torture him
until he gives up Charlie?
No.
We're missing something here.
- Yeah. that picture's
still pretty blurry.
But ERT processed partial
prints from Ron's body.
- All right. tell me when
it spits something out.
Oh. and keep digging
into Ron and Charlie.
Let's turn their
lives inside out.
What--what passes illegally
through this port?
Drugs. weapons.
counterfeit goods?
You know what. Elise?
Let's have a team talk to
the CBP supervisor at the port.
Maybe they can help
shed some light.
- Me and Ron locked horns
a few times.
but he was good people.
I can't believe
he and Charlie are dead.
- Well. not just Charlie.
His wife Mel was killed too.
- The wife too?
That's awful.
- Help us out.
How's all this work?
- Ron and his guys unload
the cargo from the ships.
get it organized
for inspection.
Clears customs.
it's free to leave the port.
Now. it's possible
that Ron and Charlie
could have made
a container go missing
before it hit inspection.
It happens. in history.
Hey. O'Dell.
lunch was over an hour ago.
Get back to work.
- You personally sign off
on every container
that comes through here?
- [chuckles]
Special Agent Bell.
take a look around.
I got 21.000 cans coming
through here on a slow day.
Meanwhile. I lost 20%
of my inspectors
to federal budget cuts.
There's just--
there's simply no way
that we can inspect
all of them.
Uh. but--
- It's the JOC.
- It's a miracle we can...
- Hey. Jubal.
Speaking with the supervisor.
What's up?
- Hey. we got a hit
on those partials
ERT pulled from
Ron Strumberger's body.
- Has the suspect got
a criminal record?
- Worse.
He's a fed.
He's the guy
you're talking to.
Border Patrol
Supervisor Wolincott.
You need to bring him in.
- Got it.
Cuff him.
- What?
- Fingerprints
were on Ron's body.
- Wait. I--
whoa. I didn't kill him!
No. I--look. I heard
about Charlie's murder
on New York One this morning.
I was spinning out.
So I wanted to go check in
with Ron.
except when I get there
I find him in that chair.
missing an eyeball.
So I--I checked his pulse.
That's it. you know?
I--I swear I didn't kill him.
He was ice-cold
when I got there.
- Well. you should
have called 911.
[soft dramatic music]
- I think I need to
talk to a lawyer.
- Why. because you're involved?
You have every right
to talk to a lawyer.
but that's gonna
slow everything down.
and the killer's
gonna walk away.
- And it will reduce
the value of your cooperation.
- [sighs]
I want immunity.
You tell the AUSA.
- All right.
we can talk to them.
but we can't make any promises.
David.
you want to help yourself?
This is your moment.
- [sighs]
I've been helping Ron
for years.
letting the odd container slip
through without inspection.
- And what were they smuggling?
- I didn't want to know.
I just took my cut.
looked the other way.
kept it clean.
- Well. there's nothing clean
about three murders.
So what changed this time?
- Ron got suspicious.
peeked in a container. saw...
something.
Got greedy.
He went to go squeeze
his clients for even more cash.
- A shakedown?
- Sure.
Ron told Charlie to drive
the container out of the port.
stash it someplace
while he went back to them.
Must have rubbed them
the wrong way.
I--I warned him. I did.
not to push his luck.
- Who's the client?
- [sighs]
I'm telling you.
I wasn't involved like that.
Only Ron knew.
- OK. what about the container?
Can you ID it?
- Sure. but it's long gone.
And only Charlie knew
where Ron wanted to hide it.
- Don't be so sure.
Let's go.
[dramatic music]
- All right. listen up.
Wolincott says this is the
container we are looking for.
and whatever was inside already
got three New Yorkers killed.
We got full cooperation
from Customs
and the Federal
Maritime Commission.
so let's find it
before anyone else dies.
What do we know?
- Uh. right.
The container in question
was loaded onto
the MV "Magaard Messina"
in Istanbul two weeks ago
by a Turkish distributor
Behrend Exports.
Now. according to the manifest.
it was coffee.
- Well. I like Turkish brew
as much as the next guy.
but something tells me
this is not about beans.
- Well. isn't java
the go-to good
for drug traffickers
trying to throw off
the scent-sniffing dogs?
- Well. yeah.
Less vital when the dogs
are on the payroll. but--
- Uh. tracking
the "Messina's" course.
it looks like the container
arrived at the Port of New York
and New Jersey three days ago.
- OK. what happened next?
Can we track its movements
out of the port?
- There are cameras located
throughout the terminals.
I'm cross-referencing with
Charlie's last few shifts.
Here we go.
- Yep?
- Once it was offloaded
from the ship.
Charlie placed it
in secondary holding.
Then two days ago.
at 12:48 p.m..
Charlie exits the port
at Essex Avenue.
driving the container out.
- OK.
Can we trace it via GPS. or--
- No. the cab isn't outfitted
with ELD tracker
and there's no GPS devices
on the container.
- All right. well. finding
a 40-foot shipping container
in New York City
should not be that difficult.
Somebody prove me right.
- Yes. I may have a way.
If I pull images from
the container's BIC ID numbers
like so.
I can cross-reference it
against street cams.
pole cams. social media posts.
- Looks like
something's happening.
- Yeah. got something.
- OK.
- It's a post from
a tagger a day ago.
Container in the background.
- Yeah.
I'm geolocating the image.
Scrap metal dealer in Brooklyn.
- All right.
get a team there now.
[tense music]
- JOC said it was here.
- First day back.
You doing all right?
- Isobel ask you
to check up on me?
- It's not a conspiracy.
Maggie.
I was gonna do it anyway.
- It's tough.
I'll be all right.
[ominous music]
OA.
Customs seal's broken.
- Well.
whatever they were smuggling
has got to be long gone by now.
♪ ♪
All I'm seeing is
what was on the manifest.
♪ ♪
Who kills three New Yorkers
over coffee beans?
[metal banging]
- Come here.
Move these.
♪ ♪
I don't think
they were smuggling drugs.
They were transporting someone.
- But who?
- So ERT obtained
saliva samples and prints
from the cans
found in the container.
We ran the DNA through NDIS.
Nothing popped.
Then we tried
the Interpol database.
and that's where
it gets interesting.
- Anzor Gery.
the Chechen bomb maker?
- Legendary bomb maker.
Yeah. red notice by Interpol.
He's on their terrorism
watch list for ties
to multiple groups
in Eastern Europe.
- Are--are you saying
what I think you're saying?
- Someone smuggled
a terrorist into New York City
and executed anyone
who knew about it.
♪ ♪
- What has Anzor Gery
been up to lately?
- Uh. so according to Interpol.
he specializes
in building highly lethal IEDs.
He's suspected in attacks
that have killed
pro-Russian forces in Chechnya.
He's also linked
to transnational
organized crime rings
operating in Eastern Europe.
who've used his explosives
to blast open bank vaults.
- Interpol lost track of Anzor
when he disappeared
in Chechnya three years ago.
RUMINT was that he was taken
to a Russian black site
or killed.
- [sighs]
And now he's back
from the grave.
- Well. whoever murdered
our victims.
they smuggled Anzor
here for a reason.
- Right. We find him.
we find our killer.
Can we tie this guy
to any known groups
operating stateside?
- Team's digging in.
So far. nothing.
- I mean. we don't know
who Anzor's working with
or what they could
possibly want on U.S. soil.
- Well. whatever it is.
we won't like it.
You know what?
Let's have our agents
press their CIs.
see if they've heard
any whispers.
- I know someone
who might be able to help.
- Yeah?
- But he's not gonna
be happy to see us.
- Us?
[siren blaring distantly]
Hey. maybe you could help us.
I'm looking for an anniversary
gift for my lovely wife.
- You've come
to the right place.
Is there anything
particular you--
- Well. you know what?
I'm gonna let her tell you.
- Do you have any of your
marquise-cut garnet pendants?
The way they catch the light
is so beautiful.
- Unfortunately. we've not had
a shipment in quite a while.
- You do not want
to disappoint my wife.
Trust me.
- Yeah. well. I have some other
pieces in the private showroom.
uh. you might be interested
in if you'd just. uh. join me.
- Mm.
- Hmm.
[tense music]
♪ ♪
- It's been a while. Ruslan.
- When you took out Alexi
and his psychos.
you told me I was done.
My debt has been paid.
- Well. CI agreements
may conclude.
but relationships never end.
- [sighs]
- Anzor Gery
is here in New York.
- Impossible.
- We have his DNA.
There's no doubt.
- We need your help.
Do you have any idea
where Anzor could be hiding?
- No.
Whatever operation
he is involved with.
it--it's quiet.
I haven't heard a thing.
- We believe the people
that Anzor's working with
have already murdered
three New Yorkers.
- [sighs]
Grozny. 2023.
Anzor set off an IED
made out of TATP.
took out a building while
attacking a pro-Russian convoy.
27 civilians dead.
You'll have a lot more death
on your hands
if you don't catch him.
- Then give us something
to work with.
- It's not my world anymore.
Agent Castille.
♪ ♪
Get out of my shop.
- All right. folks.
So uh.
Isobel's CI was a bust.
but he did mention that Anzor
had used TATP
as an explosive material.
What is that again?
- Uh. TATP. a.k.a.
mother of Satan.
favored by terrorists
because it can be made
from everyday chemicals.
- Right. So Anzor
can manufacture it
using off-the-shelf
ingredients?
- Yeah. but he would need
a lot of hydrogen peroxide.
That's one of
the active ingredients.
- But if
he is buying it in bulk.
it would pop up on our radar.
We would be aware.
- Which is why
I'm looking into
hydrogen peroxide
manufacturers.
- OK. great.
We're thinking.
uh. some bulk order.
some wholesale purchase. yeah?
- Yeah. you could do that.
Or you can buy
the whole damn company.
Look at this.
New Jersey-based
chemical manufacturer
bought out of bankruptcy
two months ago
by an offshore firm.
Crown Chemicals.
- Crown Chemicals.
Hey. Homeland. can you check
if Crown Chemicals
comes up in connection
to any Eastern European
organized crime ring?
- According to
bankruptcy documents.
one of the assets purchased
was a large stock
of hydrogen peroxide.
- Yeah?
- It's in
a warehouse in Bayonne.
- OK.
Let's coordinate
with our Newark office.
get our agents and SWAT
down there to investigate.
- Sniper on overwatch hasn't
seen any movement inside.
- There's a lot
of chemicals in there.
[ominous music]
♪ ♪
Breach it.
[suspenseful music]
♪ ♪
[chain rattles]
FBI!
Get up on your feet!
- Thank God!
♪ ♪
- Anzor Gery. keep those hands
where we can see them.
- No. no. no!
You do not understand.
They forced me!
They made me do it!
♪ ♪
You have to understand.
I never wanted to make bombs.
- Says the man responsible for
the deaths of 27 civilians.
- The blood on my hands is
a stain I can never wash away.
Three years ago.
I was abducted from my home
by Chechen separatists.
They knew what
I was capable of.
They forced me to build IEDs
to use against
pro-Russian forces
in Chechnya.
- Well. you're a long way
from Chechnya.
So how did you get out?
- When the Chechens needed
more funds for their cause.
they sold me to
Houthi fighters.
- Rebels in Yemen.
- I refused to work with them.
They were ruthless. cruel men.
They beat me.
But that only strengthened
my resolve.
until they threatened
to kill my wife and son.
I'm sorry.
but I did not want to do
what they forced me to do.
- You're telling me
the Houthis smuggled you
into the United States?
- Yes. Agent Scola.
the Houthis are here.
planning an attack.
They blame you. America.
for the deaths
in their country.
People will die.
- The Houthis are
on the ground here?
I thought they were pirates
in the Red Sea.
- Well. they're insurgents
waging civil war against
the Yemeni government--
the U.S. is unofficially
at war with them.
- Wait. where are you going?
- If there's any truth
to what he said.
I've got to make a call.
- Where's the attack happening?
What's the intended target?
- They never said.
but they needed bombs.
They made me build
two shaped charges.
50 pounds each.
Small enough to fit
in a backpack.
- Backpack bombs
means they could be
headed anywhere in the city.
- They're carrying enough
explosive power
to blow up
an entire city block.
I didn't want anything
to do with this.
You must believe me.
- OK. if what you say is true.
Anzor.
you won't be held responsible.
But we need to know
who is behind this attack
so we can stop them.
- He never told me his name.
I only heard his men
refer to him as As-Saqaar.
Arabic for the Falconer.
[ominous music]
- Thank you. Nikki.
for coming down.
- Sure. New York Station's
always happy
to help our friends. the FBI.
So Falconer is stateside. huh?
- Yeah.
What can you tell us about him?
- Well. his real name
is Hamzah al-Haddad.
He's a senior commander
with the Houthis.
He leads a unit that's been
firing anti-ship missiles
into the Red Sea for months.
Al-Haddad is violent.
He shows no mercy.
- All right.
so he's tough on his own turf.
but what about an away game?
He have the resources
to pull off an op here?
- And then some.
- Yeah?
- CIA's CT Mission Center
has tracked intel
that international
shipping firms
have been sending the Houthis
$180 million a month
in protection.
It's all under the table.
of course.
They make sure their shipments
aren't attacked
while transiting the Red Sea.
If al-Haddad is on
the ground in New York.
you've got your work
cut out for you.
- Do you have any idea
about his targets?
- Best guess.
he'll go with what he knows.
Container ship at the ports.
maybe cruise ship terminal.
- We'll dig in.
- Wait. Jubal.
- Yeah?
- Look.
[tense music]
It's Fleet Week.
We just brought the perfect
target straight to him.
♪ ♪
- Everybody listen up.
I just got off
with the Pentagon.
We believe al-Haddad
and his Houthi militants
are targeting Fleet Week.
Currently. we have
eight U.S. Navy ships
docked at piers
throughout the city
for visitation by the public.
This is Nikki Reynard
from the State Department.
She will be lending a hand.
- Don't worry. folks.
I won't slow you down.
- OK. so--so NYPD.
let's start evacuating
civilians from those areas.
Uh. Kelly. Marnie. we need
to scrub every street cam
from Lower Manhattan.
Let's see if we can
get a fix on al-Haddad.
Uh. Elise. look for
some kind of connection
between al-Haddad
and these ships.
If we can figure out
what his target is.
I think we'll have
a fighting chance. right?
- How vulnerable
are these ships?
- I mean. the Navy
has security checks.
no-bag policies. but we know
these bombs are compact.
right?
So...
- Well. al-Haddad smuggled
a Chechen bomb maker
into this country.
He can get around a bag policy.
We have a target-rich
environment.
He could take out
multiple ships.
- OK. so we need to get agents
to each one of these
Fleet Week locations. yeah?
- No. no.
It's more personal than that.
The USS "Maldonado".
a guided missile destroyer.
was deployed last year
in an anti-Houthi operation.
The Navy was trying to
protect commercial shipping.
- The "Maldonado"
was in the Red Sea.
- It had an incident
during deployment.
The "Maldonado" launched
a strike against a suspected
Houthi missile site.
It had bad intel.
The strike killed 20 civilians.
including al-Haddad's
wife and daughter.
- OK. OK. all right.
This is a--
a revenge mission.
How many sailors
aboard the "Maldonado"?
- Yeah.
a full complement. over 300.
- Where's it docked now?
- Pier 124. out near
the Throggs Neck Bridge
in the Bronx.
- Isobel.
I need to update my team.
- I'll walk you up.
- OK. we need to
spool up a helicopter.
I want a team
on the "Maldonado."
If there's a bomb
already aboard that ship.
I want to find it!
[tense music]
♪ ♪
[indistinct radio chatter]
- Captain Hannah Greene.
- Special Agents
Ramos and Scola.
- Thanks for coming aboard.
Is this the device?
- FBI bomb tech.
This is a handheld explosive
detector that will
collect trace amounts of TATP.
- Understood.
- Where are we at?
- Ship's clear of civilians.
I've got every sailor
sweeping the ship as we speak.
Nothing to report yet.
- OK.
Your crew notice anything
suspicious on today's tours?
- It's Fleet Week.
Number of tourists.
families passing through--
it'd be easy to slip away if
you knew what you were doing.
- How much of the ship did you
take the public through?
- Main deck. the bridge
where we're standing.
Never the lower levels.
- We're still gonna sweep
the entire thing.
If there are bombs on board.
we're gonna find them.
- Have we heard
from Eva and Scola yet?
- They're in mid-sweep.
Nothing yet.
- That's if the bombs
are even on board.
- Jubal.
got a report of shots fired
off 151st Street out in Queens.
right on the waterfront.
- Yeah. put up a map.
♪ ♪
It's a clear line of sight
across the East River
to Pier 124 in the Bronx.
- That's where
the USS "Maldonado's" docked.
- That's what.
2 miles as the crow flies?
- Or a drone.
- Yeah.
It's worth checking out.
Get Maggie and OA there now.
[gunfire]
- FBI!
- You the backup?
- SWAT will be here
in a minute.
- What happened?
[gunfire]
- My partner tried to cite him
for illegally parking
near the water.
[gunfire]
Out of nowhere.
he pulls the heavy artillery
and started blasting.
[gunfire]
- We believe that these men
have control over two bombs.
- Jesus. Mary. and Joseph.
- OK. we need to move fast.
Can you lay down
suppressive fire for us?
- Hey. FBI want some glory.
Let's help them out
and pin these guys down.
[gunfire]
- Go!
[suspenseful music]
♪ ♪
[gunfire]
- [yelps]
♪ ♪
- I got a Glock 22
with a switch.
- Hakkensons' killer.
Any of these guys al-Haddad?
- No.
Five shooters down.
Haddad's not here.
- Someone else.
Let's go.
♪ ♪
- Are those the bombs?
- They were.
OA?
They're on the drones.
[drones whirring]
♪ ♪
- Captain. we just got word
that two drones have launched
from the opposite side
of the East River
and are likely targeting
this ship.
- Summon general quarters.
spin up our radar.
and activate the CIC.
- General quarters.
General quarters...
- Captain. confirmed.
Two birds in the air.
bearing 357 degrees.
Range. 3.400 meters.
closing fast.
- So what's the plan here.
Captain?
[alarm blaring]
Our Aegis combat system
is offline.
Half the crew
is on shore leave.
Our close-in weapon system
isn't traveling
with a full loadout.
- Wait.
Are you telling me
that a warship the size
of a building
doesn't have a way
to combat a drone attack?
- We shouldn't need weapon
systems in New York Harbor.
- Do we need to evacuate
the remaining sailors on board?
- This is a U.S. Naval warship.
Agent Ramos.
We don't evacuate.
- This is the Shershnya-150.
a kamikaze attack drone.
Its dimensions match
the transport cases
that Maggie and OA
found on the beach.
- OK. so we got two of these
in the air right now.
- Each carrying
a 50-pound bomb.
- How long till impact?
- FAA is tracking the drones.
Based on their speed.
a little over four minutes.
- Two 50-pound bombs
can do a lot of damage
to that destroyer.
Can we just shoot them down?
- No.
No. the FBI doesn't have that
kind of anti-drone technology.
and we are not shooting bombs
out of the sky
above New York City.
- Hey.
the drones aren't autonomous.
which means
they're being piloted.
- Oh. OK. so--so odds are.
al-Haddad's in control.
Can we piggyback the signal.
control the drones from here?
- In less than four minutes?
I'll try.
- Please do!
Hey. Maggie. OA. listen up.
We believe al-Haddad
has the controls.
You need to find him
and secure that controller.
- Copy that.
He could be anywhere.
- No.
No. I think he'd want
a front-row seat
to watch that ship go down that
killed his wife and daughter.
[radio static crackling]
- Did you hear that?
- Yeah.
Oh.
Maybe the JOC can trace it.
- It's a Motorola R7.
Hey. Ian.
we can trace that. right?
- Theoretically.
but it has to be in use.
- Less than
three minutes to impact.
- OK. Maggie. OA.
we might be able
to reverse trace the signal
from the radio.
but it needs
to be transmitting.
[suspenseful music]
[radio static crackles]
- Hamzah al-Haddad. this is
Special Agent Maggie Bell.
We know what
you're trying to do.
This attack isn't gonna
make everything right.
♪ ♪
- We're running out of time.
- Hamzah.
I know you can hear me.
Hamzah.
Come on. talk to me.
I want to help you.
- You cannot understand.
♪ ♪
- Got a hit.
- OK. OK.
Maggie. keep him talking.
- Tell me why.
Why can't I understand?
- We got two minutes to impact.
- You can talk to me.
Please.
- My wife was killed.
My daughter was killed.
And for what?
Nothing.
That ship killed them.
They had no part in this fight.
- Hamzah. I'm sorry for what
happened to your family.
but killing innocent sailors
isn't gonna bring them back.
[machinery buzzing]
- Those sailors
were not innocent.
- Would your wife want this?
[machinery buzzing]
Would these murders
make her proud?
- She was more forgiving
than me.
- Hamzah. don't do this.
- Ian. please tell me
you got a location.
- No. not enough for a trace.
- You heard that. right?
He was talking
over some machine.
- Over there.
Let's try.
Come on.
- 1:30 to impact.
♪ ♪
[tool buzzing]
- This is
the clearest sightline.
He's got to be around here.
- Down there on the beach.
- Hamzah. it's over!
- Drop the controller.
- You cannot stop this.
- One minute.
♪ ♪
- Put it down now!
- Give me this.
- 50 seconds.
What's going on?
- Jubal. we have one
of the controllers.
- OK. how does--
how does she disable it?
- An override code.
Al-Haddad had
to have programmed it
when he armed the drones.
- OA. I don't know
how to disable this.
- They're locked on.
It's too late.
They will pay for what
they did to my family.
[alarm blaring]
- T-minus 12 seconds.
Brace.
- OK. you gotta try.
- What is the code?
- [spits]
- OK. I'm jamming
the drone's signal.
Try to take control.
♪
- You got it?
- Come on. come on.
[drones whirring]
- You got 10 seconds!
Five seconds!
- OK. I got one.
♪ ♪
[explosion]
[exhales]
OK.
- No.
♪ ♪
[monitor chirping]
- Eva. Scola. are you OK?
- Yeah. yeah.
A little shook up. but. um.
I think we're all good here.
- [exhales]
[soft triumphant music]
♪ ♪
- [exhales deeply]
- Great work. everyone.
♪ ♪
- You said that I wouldn't
understand what's fueling you.
I know grief. and I know anger.
And believe me when I say
I know the emptiness
you feel inside.
- You know nothing.
♪ ♪
- Copy.
Scola and Eva are on their way
back to 26 Fed.
No one was hurt.
They're OK.
- Good.
- What about you?
[soft dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- He thought that revenge
would fill the hole in him.
Nothing's gonna
make that go away.
♪ ♪
I realized something today.
I think I've been trying
to push past.
the same way I did
with my husband.
and I can't.
I'm not OK.
DiStefano killed
my baby sister.
and I--and I try to tell myself
that it's not my fault.
But I had to watch my parents
sob at Erin's funeral.
I'm the reason they're in pain.
And I try to take it
day by day.
It's like I'm not even
here anymore. you know?
Like I'm in this nightmare
that I can't wake up from.
♪ ♪
I'm never gonna be the woman
that I was before.
I don't know who I am now.
So how do I look my team
in their eyes
and say. you can rely on me?
How?
I've got to figure this out.
Isobel. because the truth is.
this job is the only thing
I have left.
♪ ♪
- Maggie. we've got you.
We're gonna get you
through this.
This is where
you're meant to be.
♪ ♪
[wolf howls]
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today